KARALIS GEORGIOS

Developer

EDUCATION

Ionian University Department of Informatics 2013 – 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Eldry - Web Developer

Summer 2016 Summer 2019

Diadrasi Taiganidou Pyton Developer July 2018

Bee Plan - Real Estate Agent July 2018 – August 2019

Eldry – Project Manager July 2019 – October 2019

Programmer – Lab of Bioinformatics (of Ionian University)May 2018 – July 2018

SKILLS



PROFILE

My name is Karalis Georgios, and I was born in Thessaloniki on 12 September 1995. I graduated from the Department of Informatics in the Ionian University of Corfu. Coding is my passion. I have worked with numerous programming languages and frameworks, Python being the most preferable.

CONTACT

PHONE: 00 30 6989060708

WFBSITF:

https://p13kara33.github.io

EMAIL:

georgekaralis7@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Football Sailing Boxing Chess Cooking

CONFERENCES ATTEDANCE

- •Genedis 2014 Location Corfu, Greece
- •Genedis 2018
 Location Toronto, Canada

SEMINARS ATTEDANCE

- •2019 7th meet-up Ministry of Testing Location Athens, Greece
- •2015 Body Language Location Giannitsa, Greece
- •2019 CI/CD: From code to deployment Location Thessaloniki, Greece
- •2019 Time management Location Thessaloniki, Greece
- •2019 Influence is success Location Thessaloniki, Greece
- •2019 Essential Skills of a Project Manager Location Thessaloniki, Greece
- •2016- Grow Greek Tourism Online Location Corfu, Greece

TRAINING COURSES

- Activating Rural Youth through Entrepreneurship Duration 6.05.2018 - 13.05.2018
 Location Alcaraz, Spain
 Further Info
- •The Data Science Course 2020: Complete Data Science Bootcamp

 <u>Online Udemy Course</u>